let savollar12 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "to anticipate",
      answer: "B. kutmoq",
      options: [
        "A. umid qilmoq",
        "B. kutmoq",
        "C. rejalamoq",
        "D. taxmin qilmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "barrel",
      answer: "C. bochka",
      options: [
        "A. idish",
        "B. chelak",
        "C. bochka",
        "D. bak"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "beam",
      answer: "A. to'sin",
      options: [
        "A. to'sin",
        "B. yog'och",
        "C. ustun",
        "D. taxta"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "casual",
      answer: "D. norasmiy",
      options: [
        "A. erkin",
        "B. bemalol",
        "C. kundalik",
        "D. norasmiy"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "caution",
      answer: "B. ehtiyotkorlik",
      options: [
        "A. diqqat",
        "B. ehtiyotkorlik",
        "C. ogohlik",
        "D. xavfsizlik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "contrary",
      answer: "C. qarama-qarshi",
      options: [
        "A. teskari",
        "B. zid",
        "C. qarama-qarshi",
        "D. aksincha"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "deliberate",
      answer: "A. uyushtirilgan",
      options: [
        "A. uyushtirilgan",
        "B. ataylab",
        "C. jo'rttaga",
        "D. atayin"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "to dissolve",
      answer: "D. eritmoq",
      options: [
        "A. qormoq",
        "B. aralashtirmoq",
        "C. suyultirmoq",
        "D. eritmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "to explode",
      answer: "B. portlamoq",
      options: [
        "A. yorilmoq",
        "B. portlamoq",
        "C. parchalanmoq",
        "D. vazillamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "to fasten",
      answer: "C. bog'lamoq",
      options: [
        "A. bog'lamoq",
        "B. yopmoq",
        "C. bog'lamoq",
        "D. qotirmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "germ",
      answer: "A. mikrob",
      options: [
        "A. mikrob",
        "B. oqsil",
        "C. uglerod",
        "D. kasallik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "kit",
      answer: "B. to'plam",
      options: [
        "A. asbob",
        "B. to'plam",
        "C. anjom",
        "D. jihoz"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "puff",
      answer: "D. tutun",
      options: [
        "A. bug'",
        "B. par",
        "C. nafas",
        "D. tutun"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "rag",
      answer: "C. latta",
      options: [
        "A. mato",
        "B. sochiq",
        "C. latta",
        "D. lattapar"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "to scatter",
      answer: "A. sochmoq",
      options: [
        "A. sochmoq",
        "B. sepmoq",
        "C. to'kmoq",
        "D. tarqatmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "scent",
      answer: "B. hid",
      options: [
        "A. is",
        "B. hid",
        "C. bo'y",
        "D. hidlash"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "steel",
      answer: "D. po'lat",
      options: [
        "A. temir",
        "B. metall",
        "C. qotishma",
        "D. po'lat"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "swift",
      answer: "C. tezkor",
      options: [
        "A. sekin",
        "B. jo'shqin",
        "C. tezkor",
        "D. ildam"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "to toss",
      answer: "B. irg'itmoq",
      options: [
        "A. bermoq",
        "B. irg'itmoq",
        "C. ushlamoq",
        "D. yig'moq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "triumph",
      answer: "A. g'alaba",
      options: [
        "A. g'alaba",
        "B. mag'lubiyat",
        "C. nishon",
        "D. muvaffaqiyat"
      ]
    }
];

export default savollar12;